nopaperforms.com 2015-03-21

# NoPaperForms | Online Admissions | Enrollment Management

NoPaperForms.com Privacy Policy

Effective Date: December 01, 2009

[www.nopaperforms.com](http://www.nopaperforms.com/) ("website") is an Internet property of TRAFFIO SOFTWARE PRIVATE LIMITED and its affiliates ("TRAFFIO," "we," "our," or "us"). This Privacy Policy is given on behalf of TRAFFIO. We are providing this Privacy Policy to you so that you can learn about our information collection and sharing practices. Data privacy and security is important to us and to our Internet users, so we want to make sure that users of our Website understand our privacy and security practices and policies. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: 

  * Access or use our Website or any of the web pages of our Website
  * Agree to receive e-mail from us and/or
  * Use any of TRAFFIO's hosted online solutions

This Privacy Policy will tell you the following: 

  * What information we collect/track about you. 
  * With whom we share the information we collect/track. 
  * How we use the information we collect/track.

  * Our policy on correcting and updating information you have provided to us.
  * Our policy on your right to opt out of some of our information sharing practices.

This Privacy Policy applies to any information you provide to us via our website, email, telephone or in any other communication or exchange you have with TRAFFIO.

Information Collection Practices and Policies

We collect information about you when you provide us your information through forms, requests for information, applications for a school (i.e., Apply Online Program), use of our service to store your data on the TRAFFIO.com profile, or through other communications and interactions you have with us via our website, email or telephone. When you submit information to us, you are doing so on a completely voluntary basis, at your sole discretion and will. Many times the information you submit is required to obtain the benefit, assistance or service you are requesting or would like to obtain from us-for instance, to use our form completion services on TRAFFIO.com, or to obtain information about a school. The information you may be requested to submit may include (but is not limited to): (1) Name, (2) Address, (3) Email Address, (4) Telephone Number, and (5) Date of Birth.

We also may collect information about you from companies that may provide us with information about consumers-for instance, from a marketing list provider. We use the following services to monitor any data you input to our site: Web analytics and Web hosting. We also may use a third party address verification service.

IP Addresses

We collect IP addresses. Your IP address is used to gather broad and specific demographic information as well as for validation purposes. In addition, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. (Please also see "Web Site Tracking Software," below.)

Cookies

A "cookie" is a small text file that a website can place on your computer's hard drive in order to collect information about your activities on the website. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you have the option to change your browser settings to decline them. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so that you do not have to re-enter it each time that you visit our Website (if you choose), and for other purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. (Please also see "Web Site Tracking Software," below.)

Website Tracking Software

Web servers, or those of third-party vendors, utilize certain tracking software to capture your domain name address (the address of your Internet service provider) for purposes of tracking Website statistics. However, we do not capture any personally identifiable information in our website tracking software. The capture of your domain name is a common practice among websites for measuring the number of hits, pages visited, and length of user session. We use this information to measure the effectiveness of the Website offerings in order to service you better.  
In addition, if you click on certain "banner ads" or other third-party advertisements on our Website that link you to third-party owned and/or operated websites (please also see "Other Websites," below), we may use tracking software provided by third-party vendors to track your "clicks" and/or your other responses to such third-party advertisements (including whether you make purchases from any such third-party advertiser through the third-party's website), to help calculate commissions that we may have earned from such third-party advertisers for such "clicks" and other responses to third-party advertisements on our Website. This tracking software may also help us and third-party advertisers measure the effectiveness of third-party advertisements on our Website. This tracking software captures certain information about your IP address and also uses "cookies." As noted in the "Cookies" section, above, you have the option to adjust your browser settings to decline certain "cookies." 

Information Sharing Practices and Policies

We may share some or all of the information we collect, as described above, with affiliated companies and with third parties (i.e. nonaffiliated companies) as permitted by law. For example, we may share some or all of the information we collect with the following types of affiliated companies and third parties: 

  * Companies with whom we conduct joint marketing campaigns; 
  * Companies that provide products and/or services, such as companies engaged in banking, credit cards, consumer finance, consumer computer products, travel, insurance, as well as other direct marketers and retailers; 
  * Companies that perform services on our behalf; and 
  * Other third parties as required by law, such as in response to a subpoena. 

Your Privacy Choices

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. If you prefer that we not share information you have provided to us with third parties, you may opt out of some of these types of disclosures.

The types of disclosures you can opt out of are:

  * Companies with whom we conduct joint marketing campaigns; and
  * Companies that provide products and/or services, such as companies engaged in banking, credit cards, consumer finance, consumer computer products, travel, insurance, as well as other direct marketers and retailers. 
  * To tell us not to share information you have provided to us with these third parties, write to us at the following address: TRAFFIO SOFTWARE PRIVATE LIMITED, Suite 401, Krushal Commercial Complex,G.M. Road, Near Shoppers Stop,Chembur(W). Mumbai – 400089.Maharashtra. India.

n addition, if you no longer wish to receive our newsletter communications, you may opt-out of receiving email communication from us by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us (see "unsubscribe" below). 

Information Use

We use the information you give us to provide the benefit, assistance or service you are requesting or would like to obtain. We may transfer aggregate or group data about our users for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage or other characteristics of our users as a group without disclosing personally identifiable information. By submitting your information to us and using our Website, you agree to allow us to transfer such aggregate data to third parties. In addition, we collect and share information as discussed above. 

Other Websites

Our website may contain links to third-party owned and/or operated websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. These third-party websites have separate privacy policies and data collection practices and we have no responsibility or liability relating to them. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and data collection practices of those sites. The privacy policies of colleges for whom we host online college applications may be different from our Privacy Policy.

Security 

Information we maintain about you is stored in a secure manner. We use security features to collect the information you provide to us via our Website in a secure manner. However, if you send us an email, that type of transmission of information is not secure, and is traveling though the Internet unprotected and can be intercepted. The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information on our registration or profile forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). While perfect security on the Internet is impossible, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the information you provide to us. We restrict access to this information to employees with a need to know this information to provide you with the benefit, assistance or service you request or would like to obtain, and to those employees that need the information to do their jobs.

Unsubscribe 

To stop receiving future communications from us, please send us an email at [support@nopaperforms.com](mailto:support@nopaperforms.com)

Changes in Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.   
The notice will tell you that we've changed our Privacy Policy and it will make available the prior Privacy Policy that applied (including, the dates that it applied). In addition, the updated Privacy Policy will list a new "Effective Date." If you continue to use our website (as described above, i.e., when you: (1) access or use our Website or any of the web pages of our website, (2) agree to receive e-mail from us and/or (3) use any of TRAFFIO's hosted online solutions, you are agreeing to be covered by the updated Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

Contacting the Website

If you have any questions or comments, please don't hesitate to contact us directly. We listen to and read every message sent to us, and we will endeavor to reply promptly to each one. Please email us with your questions or comments about this Privacy Policy at [support@nopaperforms.com](mailto:support@nopaperforms.com), or you may call us at +91-98671 84011. Our mailing address is: TRAFFIO SOFTWARE PRIVATE LIMITED, Attn: Privacy Policy, Suite 401, Krushal Commercial Complex,G.M. Road, Near Shoppers Stop,Chembur(W). Mumbai – 400089.Maharashtra. India.
